(calm upbeat music)
Welcome to our next project
and this one is gonna be the coolest
and most real world project so far.
So we're gonna apply everything that we learned so far,
including advanced stuff, like functions,
arrays and object oriented programming.
We will also learn some new stuff,
like how to use geolocation
and how to use third party libraries in our project.
But even more importantly, you will also learn
how to actually plan a project because building a project
is not just writing some code, it's also about thinking
and taking decisions and solving problems.
And so that's something I really want to teach you,
so that eventually, you will be able
to build applications on your own.
(calm upbeat music)